<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jay Ong</title>
    <link>https://www.shingjay.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jay Ong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 17:54:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.shingjay.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 - It&#39;s Only March?</title>
      <link>https://www.shingjay.com/blog/2020-it-is-only-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 17:54:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shingjay.com/blog/2020-it-is-only-march/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s only March in 2020 but it felt like the year has gone by already.
A few major things have happened in the past 3 months, namely: 1. My manager of 2 years decided to step down 2. Expedia decided to lay off 12% of its employees; my immediate colleague got canned 3. COVID-19 affecting me both personally and professionally; my day-to-day schedule has been upended and travel plans canceled. Expedia as a whole isn&amp;rsquo;t doing well and I suspect that there&amp;rsquo;ll be another round of layoffs in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.shingjay.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 17:54:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shingjay.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, thanks for stumbling onto my personal page! I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer working at Expedia. I am currently in the midst of pursuing the next stage of my fledgling career.
Some of the other things that interest me involve soccer, hiking, boxing, traveling, photography, cooking and scuba diving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://www.shingjay.com/blog/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 17:47:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shingjay.com/blog/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first blog post on a content publishing engine. I&amp;rsquo;ve been dawdling about using Jeykll for starting up a personal blog, but have never invested enough time into doing it. One day, I stumbled upon a Hugo-built site on Hacker News, and decided to finally jump the gun to doing it. I found Hugo significantly easier to use and set up; I managed to get this up and running in under an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>